<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://mack.travel/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:26:05 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mack.travel/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>bounce</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/bounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:26:05 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/bounce/</guid>
      <description>I arrived in Noosa still on the Fraser Island high and wanting to keep it going. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t hard to do so at Bounce where I spent the next 5 days. This boutique stay was the nicest hostel I&amp;rsquo;ve stayed at. It had it all: rain showers, expansive kitchen, fancy pool, sun deck, full-service bar, mini-restaurant, co-working space, nice dorm beds, air con, and ping pong. It should be no surprise that I hardly left this place while in Noosa, and I regret nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pippies</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/pippies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:37:22 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/pippies/</guid>
      <description>I spent a magical three days touring Fraser Island with Pippies Tag-Along Tours. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember how I stumbled upon this idea, but I booked it plenty in advance, and I am so glad I did it. 30 of us embarked on this adventure, led by our legendary Aussie tour guide, Scott.
Scott has been doing tours on Fraser for 6 years now, and he&amp;rsquo;s seen it all. The good vibes started with him and trickled down to the rest of the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flying whitsundays</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/flying-whitsundays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 11:00:01 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/flying-whitsundays/</guid>
      <description>The beautiful Whitsunday Islands and Great Barrier Reef viewed from above; the photos speak for themselves.
💙</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sailing whitsundays</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/sailing-whitsundays/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 10:59:56 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/sailing-whitsundays/</guid>
      <description>The Kuranda crew meets again, this time in the Whitsundays. When in Cairns, we figured out that we&amp;rsquo;d be at Airlie Beach at the same time, and we were able to book this trip together.
This was a 10-hour day spent out at sea. It was fucking hot. I used plenty of sunscreen and didn&amp;rsquo;t get burnt, but got super red and tan, along with the rest of the boat. We got to snorkel for a bit, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the same as it was in Cairns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>airlie beach</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/airlie-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:59:30 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/airlie-beach/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve arrived at Airlie Beach by way of Greyhound bus. It&amp;rsquo;s my first of 8 bus trips down the Australian east coast. I purchased an East Coast Whimit Pass, which allows me unlimited rides for a span of 30 days for a price of $415 AUD ($276 USD). Pretty good deal. I&amp;rsquo;ve met many others journeying the same way, some going up, some going down.
Airlie Beach is a classic beach town and launching point for all things Whitsundays, the popular island chain just off the coast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great barrier reef</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/great-barrier-reef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:19:01 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/great-barrier-reef/</guid>
      <description>A must-do in Cairns is to snorkel or dive the Great Barrier Reef. Every single person I met was doing it, so I thought it worthwhile. I booked this solo through the hostel.
It was an all-day event. A bus picked me up at the hostel and took me to the harbor at 7 am. The tour boat company put me at a table with other solo bookers, which was nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kuranda</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/kuranda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 20:12:19 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/kuranda/</guid>
      <description>A couple of hostel-mates were doing a scenic rainforest tour, and I joined in. We started off by taking a gondola lift through the rainforest, which was charming. There were 2 stops along the way where we could get out and walk around. The lift was taking us to Kuranda, which is a small village inland from Cairns.
When we arrived, we were hungry and found a crepe cafe where we fueled up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cairns</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/cairns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 19:45:30 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/cairns/</guid>
      <description>Cairns (pronounced &amp;ldquo;Cans&amp;rdquo;) is a wonderful gem. It&amp;rsquo;s a small town with mostly a tourist focus. There are many expeditions to take from here, like snorkeling the Great Barrier Reef or touring a crocodile farm. I had nothing set up before I got here, but the hostel reception helped me get things planned.
I&amp;rsquo;m staying at Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Oasis hostel, which has won awards on Hostelworld for Australia&amp;rsquo;s number one hostel. It features a small pool in the middle of the compound surrounded by buildings with dorms and private rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>off to aus</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/off-to-aus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 01:45:09 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/off-to-aus/</guid>
      <description>And we’re off! To Australia! I would love to go back to the land of smiles and hope to in the future, but for now it’s ownward to the world down unda&#39;.
It took me 2 flights to get here with a 10-hour layover through the night in Singapore. Changi airport was world class. It featured a free movie theater where I stopped in and watched The Matrix Resurrections. The place was huge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>farm life</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/farm-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:50:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/farm-life/</guid>
      <description>I spent a full day at the farm at Asia Scenic Thai Cooking School. I cooked 6 Thai dishes that included: laab, pad see ew, tom sab soup, massaman curry, spring rolls, and the ultra-delicious mango sticky rice. Cooking is not my primary skill, so I was looking forward to learning and eating good food.
As many great chefs and cooks know, the hard part of cooking is the preparation. The company took care of everything and made it really easy to throw ingredients into a skillet and watch it cook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pai hole</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/pai-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 10:18:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/pai-hole/</guid>
      <description>I arrived in Pai in the afternoon and I was ready to start the fun. What I knew about Pai is that it is a small, hippie, backpacker’s paradise. Most people end up staying here way longer than anticipated and it’s referred to as “getting stuck in the Pai hole”. I met many people where this was true and it almost happened to me, but I had too rigorous of a schedule that I couldn’t give up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ride to pai</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/ride-to-pai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 15:33:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/ride-to-pai/</guid>
      <description>Now on to something I’ve been looking forward to for a while, a 3-hour motorbike ride up north, through the mountains, up to Pai. This trek was recommended to me by two friends (separately) who didn’t ride themselves, but said the journey was incredible with all the views and nature. They were not wrong.
I did my own research before going and the road is famous for its many switchbacks and sharp turns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my buddy buddha</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/my-buddy-buddha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 16:45:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/my-buddy-buddha/</guid>
      <description>Today I had originally planned to travel up to Pai and had my hostel booked and everything, but when I awoke, it was a grey and cloudy day. I was looking forward to the drive the most and I decided to wait one more day to get the fun in the sun. Instead, I went on a self-guided Buddhist temple tour.
There are over 300 temples in Chiang Mai, which I think is more than any other place ever?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mad science</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/mad-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:45:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/mad-science/</guid>
      <description>I’ve wrapped up working on GymRats for now. I made substantial commits while I was here, but not nearly as much as I thought I would. The state of the business isn’t where I want it to be, but there is still positive growth and potential. Still averaging 1k sign-ups per day and continuing to see the app be essential for certain use cases. I’ve discovered some incredible, groundbreaking research related to the app that could blow things wide open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lake life</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/lake-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 12:41:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/lake-life/</guid>
      <description>Whoa, we&amp;rsquo;re halfway there. Can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been over a month since arriving in Chiang Mai and there&amp;rsquo;s only three weeks left. It&amp;rsquo;s gone by blazingly fast. That might be because I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing the same thing every day. It&amp;rsquo;s a coding groundhog&amp;rsquo;s day out here. However, I am happy to report that I went outside and touched some grass.
It was Friday and I realized I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to get done what I thought I would so I took off early and took a trip up to Huay Tueng Thao Reservoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ridin dirty</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/ridin-dirty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 08:20:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/ridin-dirty/</guid>
      <description>I’ve forgone pursuing the Thai motorcycle license. I got so far as obtaining a certificate of residency and had all my paperwork in order, but when I went to make an appointment, there was a one and a half month wait time to get one. It’s comforting that DMV’s abroad are just like back home. I don’t really get the sense that I needed the license anyways, so for now they’re tryna to catch me ridin&amp;rsquo; dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bangkok belly</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/bangkok-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:20:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/bangkok-belly/</guid>
      <description>I suppose it was inevitable. And it can happen again, so I&amp;rsquo;ll need to be more careful, but I&amp;rsquo;m just getting over a miserable bout of food poisoning. Not quite out of the woods yet, but feeling well enough to write.
It started on Thursday, and I think the culprit was the delicious salmon eggs benedict that I had for brunch. Yes, I had breakfast for lunch; it&amp;rsquo;s called brunch. The restaurant was often crowded and looked like a trustworthy place to eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>out and about</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/out-and-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:43:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/out-and-about/</guid>
      <description>After a week of being in Chiang Mai, I am time zone adjusted and no longer a zombie. This is great news as I was getting upset about it. I kept attempting to stay up until at least 9pm and kept failing and that was not a good feeling. I finally broke through Tuesday after gluing my eyelids open and made a strong determination to push through.
Even though I was waking up in the dead of night, I was still able to do some stuff during the day and enjoyed touring around some.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Für Elise</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/f%C3%BCr-elise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:29:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/f%C3%BCr-elise/</guid>
      <description>I am still stuck in time zone limbo. It feels like purgatory. I fell asleep too early yesterday and woke up again at 11:00pm. Not happy about that, but feeling optimistic about today&amp;rsquo;s attempt. Because coffee.
I spent these twilight hours reading and learning to play the piano. I&amp;rsquo;ve never given the piano an attempt and am enjoying playing it. I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to learn Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Für Elise&amp;rdquo;. It is a simpler song to learn because Beethoven made this song for a woman that he was in love with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:01:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/beginnings/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve arrived in Chiang Mai and I feel great about what&amp;rsquo;s to come. 2 trains, 3 planes, and 32 hours went by faster than expected. Normally when traveling for vacation I get really excited and have high energy. This time it&amp;rsquo;s different because I have possibly 7 months of travel ahead of me and it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly vacation.
While &amp;ldquo;excited&amp;rdquo; is a correct word to use: calm, relaxed, and happy are more accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
