<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>https://mack.travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 15:08:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mack.travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>lake life</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/lake-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 12:41:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/lake-life/</guid>
      <description>Whoa, we&amp;rsquo;re halfway there. Can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been over a month since arriving in Chiang Mai and there&amp;rsquo;s only three weeks left. It&amp;rsquo;s gone by blazingly fast. That might be because I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing the same thing every day. It&amp;rsquo;s a coding groundhog&amp;rsquo;s day out here. However, I am happy to report that I went outside and touched some grass.
It was Friday and I realized I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to get done what I thought I would so I took off early and took a trip up to Huay Tueng Thao Reservoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ridin dirty</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/ridin-dirty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 08:20:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/ridin-dirty/</guid>
      <description>I’ve forgone pursuing the Thai motorcycle license. I got so far as obtaining a certificate of residency and had all my paperwork in order, but when I went to make an appointment, there was a one and a half month wait time to get one. It’s comforting that DMV’s abroad are just like back home. I don’t really get the sense that I needed the license anyways, so for now they’re tryna to catch me ridin&amp;rsquo; dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bangkok belly</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/bangkok-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:20:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/bangkok-belly/</guid>
      <description>I suppose it was inevitable. And it can happen again, so I&amp;rsquo;ll need to be more careful, but I&amp;rsquo;m just getting over a miserable bout of food poisoning. Not quite out of the woods yet, but feeling well enough to write.
It started on Thursday, and I think the culprit was the delicious salmon eggs benedict that I had for brunch. Yes, I had breakfast for lunch; it&amp;rsquo;s called brunch. The restaurant was often crowded and looked like a trustworthy place to eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>out and about</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/out-and-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:43:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/out-and-about/</guid>
      <description>After a week of being in Chiang Mai, I am time zone adjusted and no longer a zombie. This is great news as I was getting upset about it. I kept attempting to stay up until at least 9pm and kept failing and that was not a good feeling. I finally broke through Tuesday after gluing my eyelids open and made a strong determination to push through.
Even though I was waking up in the dead of night, I was still able to do some stuff during the day and enjoyed touring around some.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Für Elise</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/f%C3%BCr-elise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 10:29:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/f%C3%BCr-elise/</guid>
      <description>I am still stuck in time zone limbo. It feels like purgatory. I fell asleep too early yesterday and woke up again at 11:00pm. Not happy about that, but feeling optimistic about today&amp;rsquo;s attempt. Because coffee.
I spent these twilight hours reading and learning to play the piano. I&amp;rsquo;ve never given the piano an attempt and am enjoying playing it. I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to learn Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Für Elise&amp;rdquo;. It is a simpler song to learn because Beethoven made this song for a woman that he was in love with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:54:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/photos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/posts/beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:01:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/posts/beginnings/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve arrived in Chiang Mai and I feel great about what&amp;rsquo;s to come. 2 trains, 3 planes, and 32 hours went by faster than expected. Normally when traveling for vacation I get really excited and have high energy. This time it&amp;rsquo;s different because I have possibly 7 months of travel ahead of me and it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly vacation.
While &amp;ldquo;excited&amp;rdquo; is a correct word to use: calm, relaxed, and happy are more accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mack.travel/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:43:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack.travel/about/</guid>
      <description>Documenting my travels abroad. Posting when I can. Photos are taken with a Fujifilm X-T30 II (XF27mm F2.8 R WR lens) and an iPhone 13 Pro. This site is hosted on GitHub pages, using hugo.
While traveling I&amp;rsquo;m building GymRats. Elixir, Swift, and Kotlin are my loves. Phoenix, Cocoa, and Compose are my muses. I work with a 13-inch, M1, 2020 MacBook Pro. It is ❤️‍🔥.
I&amp;rsquo;m learning Portuguese on Duolingo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
